A Guide to the Lester M. Salamon Papers FA1868
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Index Cards - Nonprofit, undated (Box 154)